!!!Greetings!!!
Encoded & Uplaoded By XpoZ
https://facebook.com/xpoztorrents
Raise the head.
He no longer has any milk teeth.
I would say he is 12, or 13.
Michelle, the Filipina?
Michelle?
What is your surname?
Patronym?
- Sedad.
You have a passport ?
A residence permit?
At home, at my boss's house.
Lama Bekoum.
Who is Lama?
Lama, are you pregnant?
Yes.
How pregnant are you?
Seven months.
OK,  Caritas  is going to see you.
Who is Tigest Ailo?
The Ethiopian, Tigest Ailo?
Is it you Tigest?
The hearing is open.
Zain Al Hajj.
Remove the handcuffs.
Come closer.
Souad and Selim Al Hajj.
Yes.
The complainant is in detention.
He is present and without handcuffs.
Show me your hands.
Also presents ...
His lawyer Nadine Al Aalam.
Accused are also present
Selim and Souad Al Hajj,
represented by their lawyer Saiid Tamer.
Do you know why
Are you here, Souad?
Yes, I know why, your Honor.
Why ?
I know my son
to serve his sentence in prison,
but why does he drag us here
Again, I do not know.
We are mops,
anyone can attack us!
You were called as a witness
at Zain's previous trial, is that?
Yes.
And you had testified?
And now you are accused.
Do you know why
Zain was charged?
Zain got into a dirty story
Because of his childishness.
Childish? He was sentenced
5 years in prison!
Childish?
Short...
How old are you Zain?
I do not know,
ask them the question.
Your Honor, Zain was not
declared at birth,
and he has never been registered
the civil status.
And since obviously his parents
do not know
his exact date of birth ...
Here is the report of the lymphatic doctor
which certifies that
Zain was about 12 years old
at the time of the incident.
So he is almost 12 years old?
Absolutely.
Where do you live Zain?
Roumieh prison for minors.
You were arrested on June 15
and you have been serving your sentence since.
Do you know why ?
Because I planted
a dog's son with a knife.
Did you stab someone?
Yes, and it's a dog's son.
Oh?
You insist ?
Forbidden to laugh in the room!
What's all this eddy
What did you provoke?
On the TV and in the media.
Your prison call.
Do you know why you're here?
Yes.
Why ?
I want to complain
against my parents.
Why do you want to complain
against your parents?
For giving me birth.
Hello.
I would like two boxes of Tramadol.
You need a prescription.
Who is it for ?
My mother.
Why she did not come
herself?
She had surgery on her belly.
She broke her back.
This is his doctor
who prescribed him?
Yes.
Why it's not your father
who came ?
He is paralyzed.
- You come to see who, Madam?
- My son.
- His name ?
- Ibrahim Al Hajj.
- Ibrahim Al Hajj?
- Yes.
Aunt Souad?
This way !
Massoud? It's you ?
How are you ?
How are you, my dear?
My son Ibrahim is with you?
No, they took him away
in another cell.
She's trying to talk to you!
Tell him "bye".
Say bye to your cousin.
Your brothers are all with you
in cell?
Yes, everyone.
May God protect you.
We increased the price   $ 15 a mouthful.
Our hands are busted
force to soak and wring.
Our "sock juice" is worth more
only a kilo of meat!
Be proud of you!
Get away!
- We have an exam tomorrow?
- Look at your calendar.
That's for your mother.
And that's for my pretty Sahar.
I miss her.
Rulers and ramen.
Thank you.
everything.
What fuck, father of Assaad.
Whenever it fills
the water reservoir,
we drown because of
his crappy piping!
This asshole thinks that
it's a gift ? This hole   rat?
Sahar!
It's not a house!
It's a shit barn!
Get out! You are going to be
Electrocute, mess!
- House of misfortune!
- Go live in the street.
There is plenty of room!
Zain, why the vegetables
are rotten? Did you serve Assaad?
Zain, he gave you the liquorice
and the ramen?
It's not even day, fucking!
Lick me the bunch!
Stand up, bitch!
Juice juice,
you will not be disappointed!
Sahar, come here.
Why is there blood on your pants?
Where's the blood?
Go before we are seen.
Do you remember what happened?
Your girlfriend Alia?
When his mother found out,
she locked him up at home
until the day when a big pig
came to take it.
Mom will want more of you.
She will throw you on the street.
- She'll give you   Assaad.
- But Assaad is really nice.
He is a father!
He offers me ramen and liquorice.
He'll give you shit to eat!
They will give you   Assaad,
they will get rid of you.
We will never see you again.
And he will throw you with the rats,
he will shut you up, cover the windows ...
Will not let you out.
He will give you a drop of water
every 3 days and ramen p rim .
You did not see his ear?
A rat of l'gout bit him.
Here, put  a.
You've finished ?
Yes.
Here.
What do I do?
Put it like that,
down in your pants.
Your hair is very beautiful!
Who put you on?
Show me.
So, chief, are you finished?
I still have the cans to put away,
but my mother needs Sahar.
Stay again.
I'm happy to have your sister here.
I'll bring it to you later.
I'll talk to your mother.
Bye.
Attention, do not throw
the towels anywhere.
I'll tell you where to hide them.
- You got pig?
- Yes.
You do not throw them
in the trash.
Beet juice, we like serious!
Tomato juice for the spleen!
It's   250.
Thanks bye.
Hold.
May God bless you.
Take two.
What do you want ?
- Just show you something.
- Leave me alone.
Come on, just a moment!
Fuck you, bastard.
Lick him, Zain.
Do not shit my dick!
Why enroll in school?
Out of the question. Forget and continue
work at Assaad.
Why are you complicating things?
It's not better that he goes to learn
two or three words?
Go to your heart,
but do not wake her up.
Let him go to school.
They will send us something to eat
and get dressed, for kids ...
And what does Assaad say?
I'll talk to him.
In the morning, I will go to school,
and in the afternoon
I will work at home.
Look at Farid,
the neighbor's son, Zahra.
He returns from school
with all kinds of stuff.
They will give us mattresses,
clothes ...
Shut up !
At least he'll eat there and
bring food to his sisters.
They receive the remains of the hotels
and the most beautiful marriages.
Enjoy it a bit!
Why are you so?
Inch'Allah we will see Monday.
Inch'Allah?
Do you want me to swear on bread?
I said yes.
And if Assaad gets vexed
and puts us out?
Do not worry,
he will not get angry.
We will send him Zain after school
and he will do overtime.
Soap of my balls!
Why are you mouthing?
Dtends yourself.
Will deliver a gas cylinder
Em Habib, at the end of the street.
Ms. Bahia, I'm done.
- How much is it ?
- 13,000.
Do not touch me, fucked!
Where do these chickens come from?
Who brought them?
It's Assaad, he's at home.
Assaad is up there?
Yes.
Mum ?
Assaad and his father do not care what here?
- Do not make a scene.
- Yeah, you'll see.
- What are they doing here?
- Calm down.
They discuss our rent
with your father.
I would put my hand to cut
they give you the hens
in exchange for Sahar.
Wait, listen to me ...
You're going to say this son of a bitch
that he did not do anything here.
- You do not understand ?
- Go tell him or I do it.
Lower your voice.
I swear by your sisters,
I swear by God.
That there is nothing at all here.
- So why is Sahar made up?
- She imitates me to have fun.
As soon as they finish the juice,
I go outside.
Listen, do not make me
lose your head, OK?
Go tell him that's not going to work.
Go tell him or I do it.
I do not want to hear you.
Do you want him to throw us out?
Not a word.
Welcome, dear neighbors!
Abu Assaad, serve yourself.
Thank you.
Use yourself, Assaad.
Ch rie, take your heart
and go   c t .
Removes me
this red lipstick.
You look like a witch
in this dress.
Sahar ...
Sahar!
Wakes up,
I'll take you somewhere.
- Where's that?
- I will tell you later. Arise.
Be ready when I come back.
Do not say anything to anyone.
How much until Cola?
1,000.
And if I put my sister on my lap,
1,000 pounds will do the trick?
Where is your sister?
At home, I'll get her.
No problem,
go get her.
I do not want to leave, pity ...
I do not want to leave,
I beg you.
Mom, I do not want to leave!
I kill you if you dare
put your feet back here.
Where you take her,
asshole?
You want to do
the whore of this son of a bitch?
I want to stay with my brother.
That does not look at you.
- Mom, she's a child.
- Take off your onions.
Push yourself, I tell you.
Do not be fooled by this.
You, go down.
Zain, if you still try
something, I kill you.
I understood your little game, bastard.
You were going to fuck us
in shit, little junk.
You send it wipe
the shit of this pig!
Kiss my ass,
and you go down.
You, go down.
Lick it!
She will not go to Assaad!
Little bastard!
Open the door, little asshole.
I do not want to leave, Mom!
I do not want !
Lick me!
I beg you, Mom,
I do not want to leave.
Come on, Sahar!
It's enough!
You stay here, I tell you!
I want to stay here.
I beg you.
Come down.
Come down! Come down!
Mom, pity, I beg you!
Son of a bitch.
It's enough!
I can not stand this hell anymore.
I do not want to leave, Mom!
Stop!
Y tired of your bullshit!
Get her up, shit!
Another word
and I cut your tongue!
No !
Sahar!
Let her go !
You are happy ?
Do you play the little man?
You're going to pay him dear, rascal!
Let her go !
It was to remove him from his misery.
With me, she was dead.
She barely has a bed to sleep,
Barely enough to eat and drink.
She does not wash.
Never look at the TV.
I thought, "Marie-la, at least
she will sleep in a big bed. "
A real bed.
With a blanket.
She will be able to eat her hunger.
- You did not think to arrive there?
- Never.
I never wanted that!
You believe me proud that
my son stabbed someone?
Have you considered the possibility
that it is not our fault?
I am born like that. I was elevated
like  a. Where's my pch?
If I had the choice, I would be
maybe better than all of you!
- You can not say that.
- Please ...
Now, people are spitting on me
in the street.
They take me for an animal.
I never wanted everything.
I was told, "If you do not have children,
You are not a man."
"Your children will be
your vertebral column. "
But they broke the column,
they broke my heart.
Cursed be the day
where I married.
Why I started
in this misery?
I'm not him, boy.
We have the same mouth, that's all.
But that must be a spider there,
not a cockroach.
Is not it ?
I do not need a spider,
I am Cafardman.
Why I need
of a spider?
That's it.
I am Cafardman.
What is your relationship?
with Spider-Man?
What is my link?
I'm his cousin.
So you are his cousin?
That's it. His cousin.
- What's your name ?
- Zain.
- Hussein?
- Zain!
Zain!
Where are you going, Zain?
At my grandmother's house.
- Speak louder.
- At my grandmother's house!
At your grandmother's house?
Well, she's lucky to have you.
Me, nobody cares for me.
- My life is...
- Please, the cigarette.
Please.
Stop, sir.
I'm going down here, please.
Wait, sir.
I'd like to get off here,
please.
Eat my ma ,s,
you will be my son-in-law ...
Mr. Cafardman?
The owner is there?
Sorry ?
What do you want him?
I would like to ask him for work.
What kind of job?
Whatever,
the important thing is that I work.
What's your name ?
Zain.
Zain?
And you ?
My name is Tigest.
I could clean the floor
or do the dishes, for example.
I really do not know.
Do you need an employee?
You need someone
to hold your fishing rod?
Where are your parents?
Where are they?
Sir, you would have a juice   250?
Or something else   250?
The juice is   1,000.
- You would not have something cheaper?
- No.
Go ahead.
Take it, I tell you.
Do not worry, take it.
It's busy, ma'am.
There too?
Yes, and that one is out of order.
Tigest?
You have something to eat?
Please.
Zain.
Here's the milk, OK?
You give him one   11 am,
then another   14 h.
I come home at 3 pm
You do not go out of the house, okay?
Do not let Yonas cry,
the neighbor is very boring.
Stay with your boyfriend.
I'm coming back, Yoni.
[Ethiopian]
This is your new friend, OK?
Zain is your new friend.
Are you sleepy?
[Ethiopian]
Tell him you do not have the money.
I told him, but he does not want to do
my papers for less than $ 1,500.
I absolutely have to renew them,
they will expire.
Do as you can,
but be quick.
Lots of girls are arrested.
Sometimes in the middle of the night.
You stink shit, shit!
Stop!
Take a seat.
Sit down, fuck!
It's fallen!
Sleep, sleep ...
Come on, go to sleep.
But what do you want from here?
Sleep, Yonas my little brother ...
Sleep, you'll have popo ...
Come eat corn, honey.
Bye, Harout.
Come in, enter!
Welcome!
Hot, hot, hot!
Breath, breath.
Breath, Zain.
How old are you, Zain?
I do not know.
12 years old, I think.
Do you have brothers and sisters?
Full.
- Do not they miss you?
- Yes.
The one I miss the most,
it's my sister, Sahar.
- Where is she?
- With her husband.
She's married?
Yes, and there was a drum
and a darbuka.
We had a party in the street.
People were licking
rice and flowers.
Congratulations.
Rahil Eresa.
- Last name ?
- Shifaraw.
Do you know why you are in prison?
Why are you handcuffed?
- I do not have a residence permit.
- No papers.
Where were you working?
I worked for a lady
for 6 years.
Then you ran away?
She was not nice to you?
She beat you?
No, she was very kind
but I fell in love,
and I fell pregnant
and I left ...
What were you?
I fell pregnant
and I left ...
Say, you speak Arabic well.
Do you understand everything I say?
- Yes I understand.
- So no need for translator?
No.
So you're gone
so that Madame does not know.
I was afraid that the police
separates me from my son and expels me.
I was scared and
I did not say anything to anyone.
So, you left Yonas with Zain.
When you came home,
he had taken good care of him?
You never thought
that he could hurt her?
I was scared the first two days,
but after I started
Trust him.
You expected that
Zain do what he did?
Never.
They were like brothers.
But I never wanted Zain
because I know Aspro.
Who is Aspro?
The guy who falsified my license.
Souk Al Ahad
I gave you
until today, no?
But I talked to my girlfriend.
We made him his papers for $ 900.
That your girlfriend
you make your papers then!
No but why
this price difference?
Stop your blah blah,
do not try to wind me up.
Calm down, that I can
place two words.
I'm trying to help you, there.
Who gave you the name of Tigest?
It's me.
Galope at your girlfriend
who can you do them   $ 900.
Do not do the malign.
I beg you,
I could not find the $ 1,500.
Look at that!
Does it look fake?
Nobody will entangle you
with these papers.
The woman on this paper ...
BOOM!
She exploded into a thousand pieces.
She had no one, no family.
Nobody has claimed his body.
You will be able to remove your grain of beauty,
Not needed anymore.
OK, but give me
a bit more time.
Ch'rie, I already told you that I can
save you $ 1 500.
Give me Yonas and
you will have the license gratis.
Never say again
the name of Yonas,
it's impossible for me to do that!
Your kid lives like a fugitive
in this country.
The day they discover it,
they will expel you both.
You make him live underground
like a rat.
He does not see the sun,
he will never go to school.
I suggest you give him a family.
You will be able to see him from time to time.
I know how to hide my son.
How to feed him and take care of him.
I will not stop telling you:
"Your son died before being born."
He does not exist.
Even a bottle of ketchup has a name.
With a production date
and forgiveness.
I can not hear that anymore!
How much do you miss?
- $ 500.
- Are you missing $ 500?
I can buy a human being   500 $.
So that you do not think
that Aspro is a crook,
I give you a reduction of $ 200.
And I give you 7 days.
Either you come here with the money,
or with your son,
either I never want to see
this pretty face here.
You understand ?
So take your time,
all the time you want.
Viewing.
"Hello man.
How are you, buddy? "
"Does it roll, run?"
"I saw you rolling a joint."
"Me?"
"Your mother is a big bitch."
"What a jerk of piss."
"Cocksucker thing."
"Stop your bullshit, fool."
"Asshole!"
"Damn, your mother is ugly."
Shut up your damn window!
I'm tired of feeling your food!
I'm going to make him eat shit
if she continues to annoy you.
I kill her or what?
What a shit, that bitch ...
Slut, whore ...
Are you going to...
[ thiopian] is enough,
it's up to you to recover my salary!
You know the guy.
It was you who found me the job.
I'm not the owner,
I can not give you the money.
If that's just me,
I would have given you the money.
I am Tigest,
you know me ?
You know me ?
Come back in the afternoon,
maybe the leader will be there.
No, not in advance.
We are at the beginning of the month.
You are illegal,
I already take a lot of risks.
Please,
I will do what you want.
Here is the identity card
of the boss.
I stole it for you. And you know
how much she trusts me
It is not serious,
it's for the little one.
You know what will happen to us
if they learn our story?
They will expel you with the little one.
And God knows what they will do with me.
I am only a simple guardian.
They will replace me in the blink of an eye.
- You do not even want to see his picture?
- I can not.
I beg you, leave.
Before, I worked at a lady's house.
Then, I ran away.
So, she has to pretend
for my old boss.
And to say that she does not want me anymore.
She does not want you anymore.
She will say that she wants
transfer me to your home.
So you will become my new guarantor.
My boss.
That's Jacqueline.
Who am I ?
I am not Jacqueline but Daad.
I'm going to play Jacqueline's role.
You have to work for me?
But I do not need an employee.
Oh my God,
I'm going to throw myself out of the window.
But I can not pay a good one.
I do not have $ 500 to hire him.
Do you see that cockroach?
He understood better.
If I ask him,
he can tell me the whole story.
Like all Lebanese ...
To resist and to transfer.
Where do you live?
Arax.
Apartment?
Khachik Papikian.
You give me fire, Mr. Harout?
Thank you.
Excuse me, are you smoking?
No thanks.
Why do not you want more
this girl?
I have children in Canada,
may God bless them.
They want to send me a Filipina.
They are better?
- It's more prestigious.
- It's different.
And you, you agree
to work for him?
I want to sponsor this Filipina.
With all.
I want to help him.
She is Ethiopian.
I want to offer it as a gift
my wife.
What is your business?
I have an electronics store.
Whose name is ?
Haroutchum ...
Electric.
The address of your home
where the girl will reside.
Dawra, Bourj Hamoud.
Your phone number?
09 ...
4, 5, 6 ...
Something like this.
Something like that?
This man is Armenian.
You must not take it at your word.
Give me your correct number, 09 ...?
- 3, 4 ...
- 5, 6 ...
And then 7?
He pisses us off and then
he offers us a coffee?
Thank you,
we do not want your coffee.
Thanks my God,
he did not call the cops.
He calls the police!
Yes, I am the king of Hachich ...
What's the matter ?
I look different?
Where are you going?
I'm going to call Mom.
And then    Souk El Ahad
to look for stuff.
[Ethiopian]
You're not alone, Zain is here.
everything '.
"All," Zain.
Bye.
[ thiopian] I can not
send you money this month.
I'm taking English classes.
I'm sorry, Mom.
My boss is so nice to me.
I'm ashamed to ask him for money.
I love you so much, Mom.
Rahil?
Manara?
Yes, go up.
I have not seen her since yesterday.
I thought she was sick.
She said she was going to the souk
and she did not come back.
She may have gone to Aspro.
Aspro? Who is Aspro?
It has a booth    Souk Al Ahad.
Pullovers   2 000 pounds!
Sir, where is the Aspro shop?
Aspro? It's there.
The real Aspro?
Rahil?
What is your connection with Rahil?
- We are parents.
- Are you parents?
Show me.
It's clear.
On the paternal or maternal side?
This is his son Yonas?
Is not it ?
What is Yonas doing with you?
Rahil left yesterday.
She has not come back since.
Pass me Yonas.
- No no...
- Why are you scared?
It's my little Yonas!
I know everything about him.
It's a little thug,
like his mother.
Yasser, 2 falafels
for the two rabbits!
You want to eat ?
You did not call her?
I do not have a phone.
His cell is off.
Thank you, Yasser.
- Come eat inside.
- No thanks.
What do I say to her, if she comes?
Tell him we're waiting for him at home.
- Stay here.
- No no.
Wait here with me
in case it passes.
Excuse me !
Where can I open?
Watch me  a.
- That's it.
- Thank you.
You're welcome.
You are hungry ?
No.
Good app.
What's your name ?
Ibrahim.
- And who is he ?
- His name is...
Assaad.
- And you ?
- Maysoun.
You stole it
or do you use it to beg?
It's my brother.
He does not look like you.
We are all black like him.
And...
over time, we have clarified.
How much is the box?
It depends on the car.
Let's say a woman passes ...
You look at his hand,
if she wears a ring ...
You say, "May God protect you ...
"and keep your husband."
If she does not wear a ring,
you say :
"May God send you a good husband."
Stop licking your hands,
they are too dirty.
Align, the Ethiopians ...
You are pregnant ?
[Ethiopian]
You can not say anything!
They'll take it from you.
[Ethiopian]
Yonas, my son, forgive me!
For God's sake, forgive me!
You would have something
eat for a baby?
Yes.
How many ?
250 books and   1 000 books.
I take that   250.
Gote.
Just for this time.
Without forgetting ...
It's not better
that a shawarma sandwich?
Do not swallow it whole,
you will get sick!
H !
You swallowed it in full?
Its good ?
Savor, my great, savor.
No water ?
I fuck this shitty country!
She does not ask
news from his son?
Do not try to find out how he's doing.
In fact, your mother is worse than mine.
After you, Mr. Yonas.
Go ahead.
Ibrahim!
What are you doing there?
I sell these pans.
These shit pans?
It's no better than the rotten crown
What are you on your back?
It's for the graveyard, idiot!
On the contrary,
I sell it in two seconds.
They buy me everything.
You want to bet ?
We bet a food dish.
I want meat rolls
and Chich Barak. And you ?
I would die for a dish of
Chich Barak well hot ...
My God...
but not just
what a plate, a plate  norme ...
Where are you from
your food aid?
You told me
food aid the other time.
Ah, do you mean the clinic?
I can come with you ?
But no, you're Lebanese,
I am Syrian.
Where did you find this rabbit?
Melt up your onions.
- Espèce of big goat.
- Let's go.
Can you move?
- Or do you want to taste my fist?
- Come on, Ibrahim. Let's go.
In any case I leave you the country,
I'm breaking.
Where?
I leave you the business
and all the rest.
All is for you.
Where are you going?
In Sweden.
There is a neighborhood
full of Syrians there.
Nobody asks where you come from.
They do not harass you,
nothing at all.
I will have my own room.
Nobody can enter without knocking.
I choose who can enter.
In addition, children there
die of a natural death.
I want to go with you.
Of course, but you need money.
How many ?
About $ 300. No more.
That's a lot, $ 300.
You know Os ...
Ospar?
Aspro?
Yes, in the souk.
What does he have?
This is his number.
He's organizing the trip.
He gave me this paper.
I drew a boat
Next to the number.
It's a boat
with pretty lights,
good food.
Assaad can come too?
He can swim ?
I will help him.
I do not know.
You have to ask Ospro.
Aspro, not Ospro.
Aspro.
"Where are you from?"
[Syrian accent]
"Me? From Syria."
"Where in Syria?"
"Aleppo."
- "This is your brother?"
-  "Yes, he's my brother."
[Syrian accent]
"I mean, he's my brother."
"What is his name ?"
"Nawras."
"It's been two days
that he did not eat or drink anything. "
"Why is he black like that?"
"My mother drank a lot of coffee
during her pregnancy. "
"She drank a coffee shop a day."
"Where's your map?"
I lost it while walking
by the river.
You were strolling near the river?
Yes, and the papers
fell to the water.
I could not catch them.
How did you come here?
We were at home, in Syria,
when our neighbor
told us, I think.
But I'm sure of nothing,
but I suspect it.
A shell fell on our house.
We started crawling on the Rambo.
Rambo, the one who crawls.
Have you crawled?
Yeah, like him,
in the trenches.
Well, what do you want?
What you can, but the essential,
it's milk and diapers.
Milk and diapers.
And maybe ramen
and vinegar crisps?
Arise.
What are you looking at ?
What Lamborghini!
Approach, small, that I see it.
Rahil still has not
give sign of life?
No...
I mean, yes! Rahil?
She came back
for a while !
This is ...
What is this thing
that you're trailing behind?
It's a nuclear bomb
or a rocket?
A brand new water tank.
How much do you want for
this "brand new" water tank?
- 20,000.
- 20,000?
Yasser!
Give this little 30,000 pounds
instead of 20.
Yonas ...
Why does Yonas look so skinny?
You do not eat?
He looks sick.
My God, do you smell the dog or what?
I've already talked to Rahil about it.
I told him that a family
good people wants to take Yonas.
They can take care of him,
dress ...
And you can put yourself $ 500
in the pocket.
Where are you?
So ?
It looks like you can help people
traveling in Turkey?
Do you want to travel?
I would very much like.
Would you like to travel where?
In Turkey.
I mean in Sweden.
- Turkey, Sweden, what you want.
- Which is prettier?
You choose,
I can even send you to the moon.
If you can convince Rahil
About the boy.
Okay, little?
That's it, boss.
Take  a and say   Rahil
that Aspro greets him.
Okay ?
I'll ask Rahil.
Yes, do it.
Yonas, give me the clothespin.
Do like me,
to warm your hands.
My little sister washed the clothes
because my mother was sick.
So she washed the prescription
with clothes?
I give you a plate ...
You'll have the rest when you pay me
the 3 000 that are missing.
A plate?
Give me two.
No.
Go away !
I see you approaching,
I am not blind.
Guys, are you coming to help me?
From Tramadol to the gorg e,
Do you branch?
One sip for 1,000 pounds.
Help me to wear this thing.
Come and help me !
We will agree on the price, brother.
Go quickly !
Guys, he has Tramadol!
- I have Tramadol   the gorg e.
- Would you have Viagra or Simo?
- Do you have Rivo?
- Farawla, Tradamol?
- Free base?
- I'm in the juice business.
It's Rivo, but in version jus.
You sell us salty water,
little man ?
Nothing better than seawater, man!
I have Tramadol in gorg e.
Int ress s?
1,000 pounds the gorg e.
Go, choose the country of your dreams.
Let's go to Sweden, it's the most beautiful.
We'll go with this imbecile Maysoun.
In Sweden,
no fake ass will come to you.
You can even piss off the balcony,
nobody tells you anything!
You pay what you owe him, bitch!
Take your chick and break!
I'm leaving, asshole!
Go and cook your ass.
When it is well cooked, eat it!
Do not touch the little, big con.
D gage!
Go away !
You will break the door!
What are you doing ?
Who is the son of a bitch who has changed
the lock and swing my stuff?
They are your business.
Who are you ?
I have things inside.
Your stuff is at the owner's.
Where's this shit owner?
Go see where is hiding
your girlfriend slut.
Otherwise, I call the owner.
Tell him I kiss him very hard!
Who are you compared to the other slut?
I am his brother.
What shit bag are you coming out of?
Unlock before I go crazy!
I'll call the cops!
You'll see !
If I do not break the door.
Where is the owner, brothel?
If you do not mind,
I break you in two!
- Shut up ! Shut up !
- D gage!
I. Want. My. Whore. Money !
Stay here.
Not moving.
Go back there!
Go.
Go there!
Go there.
Yes my friend.
costs ...
I'm going to send you a little kid.
He looks like a dog now,
make it a human being.
OKAY ? I have to pass it.
OK.
Why are you sad ?
It's nothing.
It's good, we agreed.
Do you have your papers?
Identity card?
I dunno.
At home, maybe.
I need proof of your existence.
An identity card,
an extract of a civil status,
a newspaper where there is your photo ...
So that I can take you out
from the port of Beirut.
Including ?
No need to worry about Yonas.
I love it, and I will place it
in a family.
And the people with whom you travel
will take good care of you.
You remember Yasser
who works for me? Go see it...
He'll send you to the hairdresser.
Then you go home
and what are you bringing back?
- Your papers.
- My papers.
Okay ?
Here are one, two, three, four ...
Here.
But you promised me $ 500.
Do you intend to drink and eat for free?
That's $ 100 for your food.
Kiss Me.
Take care of yourself. Go ahead.
It's good, you can go.
I told you that
I will take care of him.
Zain!
Have you been there since?
That does not look at you.
Where did you go?
Where? Where? Where?
I fuck you!
In any case, I did not come
to see you,
nor to see that asshole there.
- I want my papers.
- Yes ! Of course, my dear!
Selim, do you know the best?
Your son wants his papers!
Where are my papers?
Where were you all this time?
That does not look at you.
Do not look at me?
Why do you want your papers?
Do you want to work as a smuggler?
My papers, my ID card,
no matter!
Nobody has anything to wax
of you or us.
Do not play the little man,
you little asshole!
Come, you'll see,
I will give you your papers.
I have all kinds of papers.
You just have to choose.
I have papers
that will make me rot in jail.
I have an eviction notice.
And that's the paper
Most important.
Come.
Look at this paper!
It is a hospital sheet
who wants the heart.
We are less than nothing, my boy.
Parasites.
You just have to live without paper ...
If not, I'll swing you through the window
and I'm done with it.
You got pig?
Leave or I break your mouth.
Lick it, Selim!
Go tell the one who sends you that
I never made you papers!
Return from where you come from!
I fuck you and I curse
the day you are born!
Who is in the hospital?
Not a word Selim,
do not say another word!
Who went back to the hospital?
Who is in the hospital?
Send him home or I kill him!
- You junk!
- Who was at the hospital?
- Emmerner!
- Who went back to the hospital?
Talk to me.
Who was at the hospital?
What did he do to him,
this son of a bitch?
What did he do to him?
Sahar is gone.
It's finish.
She left ?
You will see what it is, to leave.
I will show you who is what.
- Come back here, little asshole!
- He has a knife!
I'll fuck you,
if you do not come back!
Come back, doggie!
I will kill you with your bare hands!
Take off the handcuffs.
You are the husband of ...
- Sahar.
She was old,
when did you pass it?
- 11 years old
- 11 years old?
A girl of 11 years
is able to marry?
She knows what marriage is?
From what I know ...
Yes, she can.
I mean she was "mother" already.
Really ?
I did not know she was a tomato
or a potato to be mother!
Zain, calm down!
I did not know
that she could die of it.
Lots of girls in the neighborhood
get married at this age.
Even my mother-in-law
was married very young.
And here, alive.
after how long
did she become pregnant?
2 or 3 months later.
All was normal?
At the beginning,
I did not notice anything abnormal.
Then she blew.
She blew a lot.
And what happened after?
He was rushed to the hospital,
with his parents.
She is deceased
At the hospital gate.
We did not manage to get her admitted.
Can I know why
they refused to admit it?
Because she has no papers.
Master, that's enough.
You bombard her with questions.
I made the slave all my life
and you dare to judge me?
By what right do you dare to judge me?
Have you been in my skin?
Did you live what I lived?
No never,
and you will never live it!
Not even in your worst nightmares.
In my place,
you would have hanged yourself!
You imagine having to feed your children
water and sugar,
because you do not have
nothing else to give them.
I am ready to commit 100 crimes
to keep my kids alive!
These are my children.
Nobody has the right to judge me.
I am my own judge.
The flesh of my flesh!
You hear me ?
The Syrian, Hussein ...
The Egyptian, Mohammad ...
You can lend us
the ear a little?
We are there, with the priest,
to meet you
Have a good time with you.
You cheer up a bit.
Come on, let's sing a song.
Zain Al Hajj, take your stuff
and go to the office.
Zain?
Zain!
What are you doing there?
Zain, where is Yonas?
Zain!
Where is my son?
Where is Yonas? Where?
What did you confide in?
My son is alone!
His eye ...
from this side,
is blue, blue, blue.
- His two eyes are blue?
- No. This eye is brown.
And this eye is blue.
You are live
on  Libert  Always.
Please go down
the volume of your task.
It's been a while since
I am your broadcast ...
and I know that you always approach
social problems ...
How's it going?
You're sick ?
Did you catch cold?
Congratulations, are you no longer in mourning?
Do not you wear black anymore?
I brought you sweets
to nibble.
Eat them, Zain.
Why do you want me so much?
I can do nothing.
I could not do anything.
It's my daughter,
my misfortune to me.
Why are you here?
When God takes you something,
He offers you something in return.
What did he offer you, God?
I am pregnant.
You're going to have a brother or a sister.
My heart hurts
I hope it's a girl.
It will be called Sahar.
Your words pierce my heart.
When you get out of here, she'll be
walking, playing ...
I do not want to see you here anymore.
You are without heart.
Leave me alone, I want to go out.
Since the death of my father,
I did not smile ...
This report on injustices
against children
deeply touched
our viewers.
Those who want to comment
what you just saw ...
09658856.
Is there an adult
Next to you, Zain?
An officer.
An officer?
Where are you calling us, Zain?
From the prison.
I hear Zain's voice.
From prison?
What prison?
It's him !
Roumieh Prison for Minors.
Zain, why are you calling us?
What can I do for you?
I want to complain
against my parents.
The boys!
Zain is on the spot!
Zain, you're live.
What would you like to say?
I want adults to listen to me.
I want incapable adults
to raise children do not have any.
What am I going to remember?
Of violence,
insults or beatings,
of the chain, the pipe
or belt?
The sweetest word I'm told,
it is: "D gage, son of a bitch!"
"Break up, junk!"
Life is a big shit.
It's not worth more than my shoe.
I live in hell here.
I burn like cremated meat.
How's it going?
Life is a dog.
I thought we would become
good people
and appreciated by all.
But God does not want
that's happening to us.
He prefers to keep mops
for others.
This child that you wear
will be like me.
Zain, what do you want from your parents?
I want them to have no more children.
Stronger.
You want them to have no more children.
Yes.
I do not think they will do
still children.
And who is in his belly?
He will come to the world, right?
We found a deposit in which
Were sequestr es 15 people ...
Stand on the line.
A little to the right.
No,   left.
Rather   right.
But that's my right.
And that's my left.
Lift the chin.
Look in front.
Mouse.
Mouse, Zain.
It's a passport photo,
not a death certificate!
=
Encoded & Uplaoded By XpoZ
https://facebook.com/xpoztorrents